Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries
NO LIVING CREATURE WAS HARMED
DURING THE FILMING OF THIS SHOW.
Faster!
Boran!
We can’t reveal Kongar’s plan.
You should leave.
As you command, my Bey.
Selamun aleykum, my Son.
Aleykum selam, Bamsı Bey.
My Bey, I couldn’t come to your wedding
because of my duty.
May Allah make you happy and fortunate.
I hope you live long
and have many children.
Thank you, my brother.
One’s legacy continues
to live with his kin.
There'll be more than a wedding.
The brave hearts want
to raise swords and shield.
We are talking about a bloody clash here
but you're talking about shields and kin…
My Gündüz...
Kin or war...
Aren’t they both like marriage?
So be it.
Perhaps when we drive
all the troubles away…
… we can talk about marriage in peace.
What about Böke?
He did his part very well my Bey.
What did he say?
Alişar is going to fall into
our trap as we want, my Bey.
So it seems Dündar Bey and
Bahadır will be escorting them.
Nevertheless, he is worried
about their numbers, my Bey.
He who fights for the cause does
not care about numbers.
One day, we will attack with
stones on our mouths...
... like Ababil birds once fought
against mammoths.
Another day, we will become David
and kill off the Goliaths.
Halt!
Today, soil will be fed with blood…
... and Erlik Khan with
death spirits, Osman Bey.
So Balgay, tell me, how much
do you trust Böke?
He is as loyal to me as a mangy
dog is loyal to his owner, Osman Bey.
Then we shall begin.
Listen to me carefully.
Preparations are
almost complete, Dündar Bey.
And my Bahadır is coming with
good news, hopefully.
I lost track of Konur.
As if the ground swallowed him.
Then, we'll play with Osman's rules.
We'll act as we fell into the trap Osman
is trying to lure us into with Balgay.
But, they'll be the ones
who'll fall into the trap.
How?
Osman told Böke that he'll
ambush me in my encampment.
Balgay and his Nöker's
will ambush my soldiers.
They'll do it
just behind this hill.
I'll wait for Osman here.
Balgay won't even guess
that I'll betray him.
They'll fall into their own traps.
Böke will earn Geyhatu's trust back.
Its time to get rid of
the malice called Osman.
He thinks we're the prey...
But we'll hunt him instead.
I shall not be called Alişar if
I don't remove Osman's heart...
... with the dagger
he took Batur's life with...
... and hang his hand in
the middle of Kayı Tent.
The Bannerlords use their
encampment as support units.
Coward Alişar will stay in his
encampment until he figures things out.
In the end, he'll attack
and try to kill us.
We'll set up an ambush here.
While Balgay is dealing with them,
I'll start moving.
I'll ambush Alişar in his
encampment before he moves.
Alişar will set his encampment up
as near the ambush location as possible.
This is the place which
overlooks everywhere.
We'll fight on three fronts.
Where is the third front, Osman Bey?
With Bamsı Bey,
we'll attack Alişar's mansion.
We'll kill his men.
Who are you calling 'us', Gündüz Bey?
Sheikh Edebali's dervishes.
They're all great warriors.
Obvious that you you won't
let that dog breathe.
It's illicit to let a
poison-breathing dog...
... live, Balgay.
About the mansion...
The mansion is everything for Alişar.
His reputation, honour...
And hareem.
The soldiers will do everything in
the city to protect the mansion.
There will be a lot of blood.
The trees of liberty are
watered with blood.
If they stay back and ask for mercy,
then our anger will also stay back.
But it's our duty to cut the blades
they're trying to cut us with.
Its time to feed our weapons with blood.
You know where to find me
once we're done, Osman Bey.
The child's birth...
... we've been dreaming of...
... and suffering from...
... is today.
We take our fame
from our ancestors...
... and today, we'll pass it
to our grandchildren!
Since we came here for holy war...
... then we'll form a unit whose only
desire will be holy war, shaded...
... and justice.
We'll establish a Beylic.
We'll establish...
... a state.
- Allahu Akbar!
Dündar Bey. You will go to the place where
Osman will set up an ambush with Bahadır.
As the Bey, my soldiers will be
under your command.
With Böke, I'll hunt Osman who swore
to attack me in my encampment.
Water follows water,
blood follows blood, Alişar Bey.
Osman is mine. He still has
my son Batur's blood on his hands.
Dündar Bey...
I too, want to take Osman's life.
But we need to hold him before Geyhatu
when he comes here.
We can't get our point across
if Geyhatu doesn't hear for himself.
What if Geyhatu doesn't
give him back to us?
What if he kills Osman himself? Then
what'll happen to my revenge, Alişar Bey?
I'm after the hyena,
you're after the leather.
It'll be as I say.
But if you don't care about what I say...
... go back to where you came from.
Father!
Alişar Bey!
It's not the time to fight!
I understand your pain, Dündar Bey.
But...
This dagger will enforce its rule.
Doesn't matter if Osman is dead or Alive.
Keep a stiff upper lip.
You're right, Alişar Bey.
We need his dead body.
It's enough if I see vultures
eating Osman's corpse.
- Gonca!
- Bala!
Welcome, my daughter.
Thank you, Selcan Hatun.
My Bala!
Gathering supplies for
the lodge took long.
I couldn't make it to your wedding.
But we'll be together in the feast.
- Hopefully, my Gonca. Welcome.
- Thank you, Bala.
Come on!
My Sheikh!
We've prepared the dowry, my Sheikh.
We'll go to the Tent if you allow us.
These dowries are temporary, Selcan Hatun.
We'll send it with someone.
The real dowries of those who have...
... strong faith, are shaded.
This is the day of Ahiyans, Bacıyans.
The duty waits for you.
Give us your orders, my Sheikh.
Osman Bey is on the road for a holy war.
He's after liberty and justice.
Supporting him in his cause is
the reason of life for us.
What's our duty, my Sheikh?
You'll join the attack
to Alişar's mansion.
You'll destroy that origin of unrest.
You'll show to the whole world how
those who pray at night...
... can be fighters in the morning.
Come on. Your horses shall be fast
and your weapons shall be sharp.
As you order, my Sheikh.
Cerkutay! Tell the Nökers.
No one will attack before I say a word.
The Nökers in covers will stay in cover
no matter what.
If they have to, they must
go back to cover.
Don't kill Dündar.
That's for Osman to do.
As you order, Balgay.
Commander Balgay! Do you think
Osman is playing with us again?
- He's nowhere to be seen.
- Don't worry.
Osman is as crafty as a wolf.
He knows that he can't deal
with Geyhatu without me.
That's why he can't do wrong to me.
I don't know why we're
involved in his fight with Alişar.
Instead of him joining our fight,
we're swinging swords for him.
Alişar isn't only fighting with Osman.
He worked with Geyhatu and destroyed
all my plans.
Geyhatu will be very angry if he finds out
that we worked with Osman to end Alişar.
We'll take no prisoners.
The dead can't talk.
Osman will be responsible for this for
being in beef with Alişar.
So Osman will feel Geyhatu's wrath.
While they fight,
I'll destroy both of them.
I'm behind you until the whole
world kneels before you, Commander Balgay.
Bless your new position.
My Bey. You were right.
The vulture is waiting to end us.
- Dogs!
- As if he wasn't controlling Dündar Bey.
He's throwing him into the fire.
Coward!
My Bey! Alişar is ours.
Let's go and end him.
Brother. The road to victory
is full of disorder.
- Don't forget that.
- My Bey.
I'm always honoured to fight with you.
If I die, I'll die with gratitude towards
you and my Allah.
Thank you, brother, thank you!
This is our first revolt to the Mongols
and their supporters...
... who settled on
the destroyed Seljuk throne.
May Allah help us in this cause.
- Amen!
Let's go!
Clouds of gloom are all over you again.
I'm afraid of that cursed Osman, Aygül.
I can't relax before your father
returns safe and sound.
Don't worry.
Wait for Osman to stop breathing.
Burçin! You look worried.
What happened?
Did something bad happen, my daughter?
Demirci Bey's daughter visited.
Bala Hatun's dowries have arrived.
They married with Osman, it seems.
They're nowhere to be seen.
But everything is already at the Tent.
All the Beys are in the caged tents.
It is said that they'll be executed.
My Allah...
May Allah almighty help our Beys.
Osman...
May your tricks backfire on you!
While you're dreaming about
going to sleep with your wife...
... you'll be hugging snakes
in deep pits, Osman.
We're almost there.
Where are you headed to?
We're bringing fruits and vegetables
to Aygül Hatun's mansion.
Fruits and vegetables.
Alişar...
You also came, huh?
You don't have beef with me.
Too late for you to realise, Alişar!
Cut his head, put it on a spear and
place is somewhere Osman Bey will see.
I promised you victory and victory only.
What awaits those who support Balgay,
you say?
Wealth! Fame!
- Balgay!
Balgay!
Ambush!
I brought you death!
I brought you death, Balgay!
Death!
Ambush! Take Cover!
Archers! What are you waiting for?
Swords up!
- Let's go!
- In the name of Allah!
Ya Allah!
Come to your death, Osman.
Alişar!
Get out of the place you're hiding in!
Come on!
Here I am.
The most powerful will be victorious!
Come here!
Attack, valiants!
Böke! I need Osman alive.
- They're getting suspicious, Bala.
- Our wedding feast is ready then.
Aygül Hatun has no such orders.
go back.
How can that be? Adelfosmo!
Give him the documents.
In the name of Allah!
- Ambush!
- There's an ambush!
May blood rain upon the degenerates!
Ya Allah!
- This way!
- Run!
- Ambush!
- They're looking for trouble!
They went too far
by attacking the mansion!
Come on! Go, soldiers!
Run!
They're here. So they were
planning for this!
You! Look at me! Tell everyone inside to
close their windows and take their swords!
Ya Allah!
Karapolat! Get your steel sword up!
Allahu Akbar!
Hit then, valiants!
For the babies and martyrs!
Allahu Akbar!
Close the windows and cages!
Quick! Let's go!
This is the Bannerlord's mansion!
If Alişar Bey isn't here, his Hatun is!
Don't let them through!
I'd rather die than be captured by them!
Let's go, soldiers!
Run, soldiers! Quick!
Come on!
Go! Never surrender!
Surround the place!
Don't let them get us in the back.
Let's go!
Go downstairs! Come on!
We won't surrender!
We won't resign either!
Bring it on!
He is out of arrows.
Let me deal with Balgay.
When did you forget the days you crawled
to my presence for help, Dündar?
Yesterdays are over, Balgay.
Now you're mine!
Fool Dündar! Even your wife Zöhre
is smarter than you.
She knew who to ask help from.
You'll die!
I'll make a drum from your skin
and play it in Kayı Tent!
Do you think I'm like the young Osman
you're working with?
Maybe I'll ascent to heaven from here.
But I'll take you with me.
Balgay! Come here.
Come here and taste my sword!
Come here!
Cerkutay!
You take Balgay out of here.
I'll deal with them.
Young Osman...
Young, mad Osman...
Osman who opposes the state...
You're in the Bannerlord
Alişar Bey's arms.
Now, your end is certain.
I've come to take the Mongol's
leash from your neck, Alişar.
You'll get your freedom
after I take your life.
You talk too much
but you're too dumb, Osman.
I'll torture you until you
beg me to stop like a dog!
In the name of Allah...
Attack, valiants!
If Alişar finds out that Böke is lying,
then what will we do, my Bey?
If you turn your back to the enemy,
you'll lose the war, Boran.
Böke is an enemy,
just like Alişar and Balgay.
We'll be cautious.
I can't push my valiants into a war
by trusting Geyhatu's dog Böke.
Ambush within ambush, Böke!
Alişar is running away, my Bey!
Böke! You go that way!
Alişar!
Come at me!
Kill them all!
All of them!
The oppression is over, my Gündüz!
It's over!
It's over, Bamsı Bey! Over!
I'll sacrifice countless goats after
I see this place burn to the ground!
Hopefully!
I'll sacrifice goats! Come on, valiants!
Break this door!
- Let's do it!
- Come on!
Come on!
Come on, valiants!
For my Aybars! For our martyrs!
Come on!
Aygül Hatun! We can't hold much longer!
Escape! Save yourself!
Shut up!
- We can't deal with them, Aygül!
- Aygül!
- We can't waste our lives!
- Let's go!
No one leaves!
Come on, valiants!
For our martyrs!
Allahu Akbar!
- Allahu Akbar!
Let's go, I say!
We'll deal with them tomorrow, let's go!
It's a catch if I can get one of them!
Everyone will stay here!
We won't let them get the mansion!
We're surrounded!
Where will we escape from?
How will we get out of here?
There's a secret passage!
It leads outside.
We'll get to safety without
anyone seeing us. Come on, Aygül!
Valiants! Take the battering ram!
Come on!
Allahu Akbar!
Come on, valiants!
Come on!
Allahu Akbar!
In the name of Allah!
Where is Zöhre Hatun?
They escaped from the secret passage.
Selcan Yenge?
I couldn't sit while all
this fight was happening.
I have a score to settle with Zöhre.
I'll go after them.
- Let's go! Move!
- Move!
Osman won't stop following us.
Cut him off!
Come now, Osman.
Geyhatu won't kill you...
...I will.
Useless fool!
Father!
Won't we go after Balgay?
Do you think I care about Balgay?
Let Alişar's men go after him.
Osman is unpredictable.
We shouldn't leave Alişar alone.
I told you to stay calm but...
...I'm confused as well.
He goes after Osman but sends
us here.
And ever since the thing with
Melik, I'm disturbed.
What if Osman is right?
What if it was Alişar who killed
my brother?
Then, I will take such a revenge that...
...all the world will hear it!
If it is true, then it will be us
who the world will be talking about.
What about my sister?
Huh, father?
How will she recover from the shame of
being in the same bed with...
...the killer of her brother!
We need to go to the encampment.
They are waiting for us.
Move.
Hurry.
Here...
...I'm in front of you!
Come on...
...let's finish it.
But a sword raised against me...
...is raised against the state.
Sheathe your weapon while you have
a chance.
Let us reach an agreement.
The state of yours which steps
on the Laws of Turks shall be ruined!
May you lay under its ruins, Alişar!
From now, your state is no more...
...both to me and to Turks.
What will you do?
Will you have khutbahs in your name?
Will you make your own coin?
Young boy...
Mad boy...
Where you and your lineage will
end up is...
... graves without al-fatehah!
They will read al-Fatihah for us,
even after thousands of years.
But you will only be remembered
by shame!
Die, then.
Alişar...
What is it?
Are you going to kill me?
C'mon, do it!
There is no easy death for you,
Alişar!
You took my honor, my position...
...everything I had!
What are you waiting for?
Kill me!
Poke my eyes out, skin me alive...
...let my blood run over my body!
What you say fits the Mongols which
you're a slave of.
In these lands which my father conquered..
...I will put you in a grave but no one
will know where it is.
Mashallah!
This flag has been the symbol
of justice...
...rights and laws.
May the light it gives...
...illuminate the whole world.
The bow frightens tyrants...
...the arrows...
...gives hope to the innocent.
May the shadow of this flag...
...be a shelter for...
...all the poor!
Mother, they went this way.
Aygül.
-What are you waiting for? Move.
-Go, mother.
They must be after us.
If I don't remove the tracks we will
all be captured.
Let Burçin go...
...and stay with me.
Do as I say, mother.
I will find you later.
Don't look behind.
Move.
Aygül.
They came here.
Tracks show this way.
It's still fresh.
We should follow.
Are you looking for us, Dündar Bey?
So...
...so, it was a trap.
I won't let you take my
father while I'm still alive.
You will kill me first!
And I won't let my son be a
cover for me.
Either you will kill us...
...or we will kill you.
Come on!
We didn't come here to fight,
Dündar Bey.
We didn't come here to fight.
What is this gibberish?
Speak!
You are too blinded to see the truth,
Dündar Bey.
We need you alive.
Not dead.
Böke! Kill him!
Kill him!
When I was about to kill you,
you said that I was wrong.
Let's see who is wrong now.
That is for another day, Böke.
You came to my house!
Shame!
Lower your weapon, Aygül.
I don't want to see you bleed.
You thought I ran away!
But I don't run away.
Especially not from you!
From now you don't have me.
If you make another move,
you will die.
You spoke truly. I never had you.
You are a clapper for those who
step on our laws...
...and a nebbish that helps
those who think they are a Bey..
...by killing a Bey.
Look.
Do you see?
They did everything they could...
...and took the throne my father...
...who is the real Bey.
Now they are bloodthirsty because
he wanted his right.
These are people who give up
on their own lives for a throne.
Speak! Who are you?
That Osman who made you fly
high in love...
...will let you down, too.
When you stand against him,
he will do the same to you.
Don't get happy that
you are a bride now.
Wait, Bala Hatun.
He is my Bey.
He knows the best.
You should think more about...
...what will you do now.
No...
No, I can't...
I can't leave Aygül alone.
I will go back.
Don't, Zöhre Hatun.
We can't handle them.
They won't hurt Aygül.
But they will kill us.
You leave and save your life.
I can't leave my daughter alone.
Dündar Bey and Bahadır entrapped
Balgay.
From now, you are alone, Osman.
They both are captured.
They are on their way.
My warriors will bring them here.
They will face justice just like
you will.
And about Gündüz Bey
and Bamsı Bey...
They went to your mansion...
...which is more unholy
than Byzantine palace.
From now, both your mansion...
...and your flag is on my hands!
You are nothing, Alişar.
Nothing.
Prepare your horse...
...to take that dog away.
- Yes, my Bey.
- Move.
You were a dog to Geyhatu who wanted
to overthrow the emperor of Byzantine.!
You caused the deaths of many people
from your blood.
Now...
It's time to pay, Alişar.
Osman...
Statecraft, Osman.
It is nothing like the mind of a shepherd.
Such a shepherd that...
... he stopped all your plans
with Geyhatu.
Sofia became the Emperor's prisoner.
We went to the Emperor and gave the names
of the Monks of Margareth.
Your uncle...
Sungurtekin...
He was in this from the beginning.
Be afraid of Geyhatu's wrath, Osman.
What kind of a devil are you?
First, you killed Batur.
Then, you married Aygül.
You caused a civil war.
Am I the devil?
Or is it Dündar?
An ambitious fool who set his eyes
on the throne of your sick father.
With few words, he saw you as a rival on
his way to the throne...
...and he became your enemy.
He didn't doubt that you killed
his son.
Nor did he doubt about giving
his daughter to me.
If you are looking for a devil,
look among you, Osman.
Among those who come after...
...your grandfather Süleyman Shah.
Alişar!
Fool.
Control your anger, uncle!
You are late, uncle!
You are late!
Batur...
Osman... Osman, I...
What have I done?
Batur...
My son...
Uncle...
Uncle, uncle!
Uncle. Uncle!
Get up!
My boy...
My Batur...
Alişar...
Hang on, just a little bit more.
Selcan Hatun!
Let my daughter go.
Let us part our ways without blood.
So, you don't want blood, huh?
She has a golden heart.
If is that so...
...come and get your daughter.
I say let Aygül go.
Confronting the Bannerlord does
not benefit you.
By thinking of benefits, you gave your
daughter away.
I don't need any benefits.
If you didn't go mad about the throne...
...that banner lord would help the
whole family...
...and the tent.
But everything happened because of your
ambition.
Alişar...
How did you do that to my son...
...to my daughter...
What kind of a conscience is this?
What kind of?
You gave a son for the tent.
Wasn't it you who said that...
...I'd give a thousand son
to my tents.
Huh?
Uncle.
Uncle!
I had the killer of my son marry
my daughter.
Osman...
...my nephew, forgive me.
I was a victim of my ambition.
But don't spare my life.
Forgive my Bahadır.
I took him to this path...
Forgive him.
Now swing this black weapon of yours...
...onto my neck.
Behead me.
Finish me.
Osman...
...don't let me live with this shame.
Because of my ambition and stupidity...
...I have the blood of my child on
my hands...
...dignity of my girl...
How can I look Aygül on the face?
I ruined the lives of...
...both my children.
Come on, Osman.
I don't deserve to live.
Take my life.
Come on.
Uncle...
...the decision about you...
...will be made by my father.
But...
...you will get what you deserve.
We wanted to be united.
To face the difficulties together.
But we couldn't convince you.
It turned out that you are not the one.
Whatever I can say to you, it is not
enough, Zöhre.
Do you know what they say?
'Ignoble' that's exactly what you are.
Murderers.
Murderers!
Balgay.
Haven't I told you that warriors on cover
will not leave their position no matter what!
Kongar was leading them.
It's his fault.
Enough! If it wasn't for Kongar...
...you would be dead.
You are bleeding too much.
We need to brand it.
Kongar will find our tracks anyway.
Come on.
Osman.
Balgay.
-Are you alright?
-You sold me out, Osman.
I was going to die because of you.
We need to take this arrow out.
What are you waiting for, Cerkutay?
First, you ambushed us.
And now you are trying to help, huh?
I don't need anyone's help!
I didn't set the ambush.
It was Böke who you trusted much.
He sold us both out.
But...
...don't worry.
I killed him.
Who betrayed isn't important.
My Nökers were slaughtered.
And my condition is...
From now on, we'll do as I say.
I got what I wanted, Balgay.
But...
...I will still keep my word to you.
On your battle...
...I will help you kill Geyhatu.
But...
...if the Noyans you will bring are
like Böke...
...this time it will be me who will
kill you.
When I return, everything will be
different.
Now you got what you wanted.
Now you are in my debt.
A valiant one doesn't forget
his debt.
I don't forget anything.
Don't die until we get even.
Those Nökers on the cover...
...I ordered them to stay.
You will answer for this.
Kongar was leading them, Kongar.
-Selcan Hatun.
-You got her.
We did, Gündüz.
I will see you later.
You will answer for capturing...
...the real Hatun of Kayı.
Bamsı Bey...
Don't listen to her.
Who are you to listen to us.
The only thing you know is using a weapon
and overthrowing a Bey.
Come on.
Take them away. Come on.
They ambushed us.
She tried to kill Bala.
She got wounded in the fight.
Burçin... Burçin, my girl.
You will be fine.
Burçin, you will be fine.
I promised to your father.
Who did you side with, Burçin?
How did you end up with
these snakes?
Take her to the doctor right away.
She needs to be tended.
Hurry, hurry!
Gonca Hatun, you are wounded, too.
Go with them. Take her to the doctor.
-Go, go.
-Bamsı Bey.
She is severely wounded.
She lost too much blood.
You should know.
May Allah help her.
You are victorious, Osman Bey.
We are just followers of Allah, Göktuğ.
Allah is victorious.
I was with Balgay.
His wound is deep.
But that wound won't kill him.
They are waiting for you.
No, Osman Bey, no.
There is no easy death for him.
I won't let him pass away before
paying for his deeds.
Don't worry. He won't have an
easy death.
Then, give me the word, Osman Bey.
Give me the word and I'll take his life.
Let him pay for his sins.
Now is not the time, Göktuğ.
I can't get rid of Geyhatu
without his help.
He needs to live a little longer.
I talked to Balgay.
His intention is having you
fight with Geyhatu.
He dreams of killing you both after
you weaken him.
I know, Göktuğ. But there still some
things I need to know.
So, you will go to him.
As you wish, Osman Bey.
Göktuğ, your mission is difficult.
You will be a companion to the killer of
your father and your people.
This isn't a thing any warrior
can do.
Your job is important.
Because of the news you will bring,
many poor people will live in peace.
But if...
If you say that you can't...
...know that I won't despise you for that.
My Bey, be at ease.
I'll do whatever you order.
Osman Bey.
Protect my brother.
Don't worry, Göktuğ.
Your brother is my brother.
Thank you.
May Allah help you on your way.
Your father...
...Oytun Alp...
...when you were a baby...
...at an ambush against me...
...sacrificed himself.
My Allah is witness...
...if it wasn't for him...
...I was going to die.
He gave his last breath...
...on me.
He put his holy head...
...on this knee of mine.
He looked at me...
...as if he was begging...
...he looked at me as if he was begging...
....but not because he was afraid...
...not because of that...
...his only concern was you.
So, he looked at me like that...
...my Burçin, he said. My orphan girl.
Now...
...she is an orphan.
Burçin, he said...
...is under your protection.
Her head should be up, he said...
...she is a daughter of a martyr, he said.
On his last breath...
...he wished for you, Burçin.
He wished for you on his last breath.
I didn't want anything to happen to him.
I wouldn't want that.
But it happened.
And you spent whole your childhood...
...with holding a grudge.
I knew that you would never
forgive me.
But...
...but then you fell in love.
You loved my Baybars.
You looked at him like he
looked at you.
Then, you grew up...
...you came to kiss my hand.
''Father, father!'' you said.
You aren't responsible of anything.
You raised me.
You were a father to me, you said.
I believed you.
I swear, I believed you.
I swear I did.
I thought that the fire in your heart...
...gone away for good.
But...
...I couldn't know that...
...your grudge would revive after
his death.
I couldn't know.
I couldn't know, my daughter.
Burçin.
My girl.
Open your eyes, open your eyes!
Come on, come on, open them.
Father...
Yes, my daughter, yes.
Yes, speak, my girl.
Forgive me.
My girl, open your eyes.
My Burçin, open your eyes.
Woman, woman, woman!
Come here!
Come here at once!
She opened her eyes!
She spoke to me!
Then closed them again.
Check her.
-I'll do what is needed.
-Yes, yes. Do what you need to do.
Hang on, my girl. Hang on.
Come on my Burçin.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
She is my daughter.
Come on, my daughter, come on.
Come on.
Burçin, daughter.
My Aybars, your fiancee...
couldn't meet his lover, but...
He will meet his eternal lover.
Daughter, Burçin...
your fate is...
due to the last judgement.
If it was a little bit stronger, it'd
destroy your liver.
Erlik Han gave me an opportunity for
revenge.
He gave me an opportunity to
take my soldiers...
and show everyone who is in the power.
Let's go.
Commander Balgay, how is your wound?
Are you okay?
- Rest a couple of days, if you want to.
- We don't have that much time.
We are setting off with Cerkutay
as soon as possible.
Tell me, why are you so late?
Where have you been?
After I saved you, I followed Dündar
to ambush Dündar.
But Osman acted before me,
and I returned.
I owe you my life, Kongar.
Wish anything from me.
Revenge.
I wish for revenge, Commander Balgay.
I wish to come with you to kill the ones
who disobey you.
I have my full trust on you.
You will stay here.
Keep a sharp scout.
So, you wish to be with me.
Okay then, you can come too.
Our way is rough, and I am wounded.
- You will have plenty to do.
- As you command, Commander Balgay.
Then, let's go.
When we return, there will be a new era.
Go!
Traitor!
- Finish him, my Bey!
- Don't let him live!
Alişar...
Alişar!
Alişar, who sold his soul to Mongols,
became their dog, and bossed around!
Osman!
You'll pay for what you've done, Osman!
I will make you regret this!
I will kill you all!
Kill you all!
Don't make me cut your toxic tongue!
This infidel was trying to...
raid our tribe with his soldiers!
In front of my father's blessed tribe,
he tried to call us account!
Let everyone hear this!
This devil is behind all of the
dirty cases.
Batur's murderer is this dog.
Murderer!
Damn you!
As to my uncle Dündar, and Bahadır...
They get egged on Alişar and
betrayed the Beys of the tribe.
However, my father will decide
their fate.
I am ashamed of tellling Aygül...
what you have done.
Now, go and tell everything to
your daughter.
This shame will be enough for you, uncle.
Go.
Imprison him in a tent.
Put two Alps on him.
- Father.
- My Bey.
It's long.
My husband is about to be executed,
you are doing nothing, father.
Whatever it is, tell me right now.
Where is Alişar Bey? Where is my brother?
Don't push your father, do whatever he
says. Let's go to our tent.
Please, tell me father.
What are you hiding?
Batur's...
Batur's murderer is...
not Osman.
Then who?
Who?
Alişar.
It was Alişar.
My Daughter.
Did you send me to my brother's killer?
Aygül, Aygül, daugher, don't do it.
You are my reason, father.
Daughter, don't do it Aygül.
Please, don't do it, Aygül.
Aygül!
Don't do it, daughter.
Don't.
Brother.
Brother, brother.
The blood of this dog, who bothered
our tribe, our valiants, our honor....
Our Bey deserves it.
Before me, this privilege...
is my brother Osman's right, he
brought him into line.
Osman Bey.
You'll be a trouble for your tribe
as well.
Don't do it, we can talk,
come to an agreement.
This is bannerlord talking to you.
The penalty for this will be rough.
Think it through, only I can save you
from Geyhatu.
The only power that can protect us is
my Lord.
You can't even protect your honor.
Osman Bey, don't, listen to me.
Listen to me, listen to me.
Look, we can come to an agreement,
listen to me.
Geyhatu's dogs.
They smelt the blood.
Sufutay.
I am Noyan Sufutay.
I am here as the messenger of
blessed Geyhatu.
Release Bannerlord Alişar right now.
And deliver me that rebel Osman.
Otherwise, not only Kayıs...
but all the tribes in this land...
will be slaughtered.
Noyan Sufutay.
I am Gündüz Bey.
We die one, resurrect a thousand.
However, we are not delivering
my brother Osman Bey.
Are you disobeying the order
of blessed Geyhatu?
Damn Geyhatu. Is he bigger than Türk's
laws to ask me to forgive this dog?
Geyhatu doesn't ask, Geyhatu orders,
Osman Bey.
We trampled your laws when we
conquered Konya.
In this tribe,
there will be my wedding tomorrow.
Tell Geyhatu, if he is to take my life,
let him come.
Kayıs are not like the ones who sells
their freedom...
just to live, and give up on their honor.
If he is strong enough to rule us...
let him come!
Are you challanging Geyhatu,
Dark Osman?!
Forgiving cruels is cruelity
for the oppressed.
Neither our tradition nor our religion
approve this.
Now, tell Geyhatu.
From now on, in this lands we conquered...
there will no longer be cruelity.
Justice forever,
Freedom forever!
Allah-u Ekber
(Allah is the greatest)
Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries